assh.org 2008-12-16

# ASSH | Privacy Policy

[Home](http://www.assh.org/) Privacy Policy 

In an effort to maintain efficient service while respecting the privacy of ASSH website visitors, ASSH has created and posted the following privacy policy. 

**Information Collection and Use**  
We will collect personally identifiable information that you provide to us, including your name, employer's name, address, telephone number, specialty, and e-mail address. ASSH may use and store such information in order to notify you of official ASSH business, provide a product or service you requested, secure your membership status, evaluate member and prospective member needs and interests, and alert you of ASSH news, activities, services and benefits. Personally identifiable information may be given to a third party in order to complete a specific business transaction on behalf of ASSH. Contact information from inquiries received by ASSH may be shared with ASSH members to provide a service, satisfy a question, or develop a prospective business relationship. 

**Registration and Order Forms**  
To attend events, meetings, conferences and request products, you may be required to fill out a registration or order form and provide personally identifiable information which we will use to process your registration or order. In addition, your name and information may appear on registration or attendee lists distributed at ASSH events, meetings and conferences to other attendees and third parties. 

**Cookies and Log Files**  
Cookies are pieces of stored information used to provide smoother navigation throughout the website, such as a saved password; to identify user trends, such as page views; and for other internal purposes, such as assessing the effectiveness of our website. You have the option of setting your computer to disable cookies or to alert you when cookies are being used. If you choose to disable cookies, please be aware that portions of the ASSH website may not function properly. 

**Links**  
There are links to other websites throughout the ASSH site. Please note that ASSH is not responsible for the privacy policies of these other sites and hereby disclaims any liability or responsibility in connection with such linked sites. 

**Security**  
Online registration and information such as credit card numbers will be secured using a commercially accepted method of encryption. However, while we employ reasonable security measures to protect your personal information, please be aware that no method of electronic transmission is completely infallible, and we cannot guarantee its absolute safety. 

**Updating Personal Information and Participation**  
At any time you may contact ASSH at info@assh.org to update your personally identifiable information, opt-in to, or opt-out of any service. We will provide opt-in and opt-out opportunities as applicable to the service or product being offered. 

**Privacy Policy Updates**  
Should any changes be made to this privacy policy, we will post them on this page with appropriate explanation. 

**Acceptance of our Privacy Policy Terms**  
Using the ASSH website indicates your acceptance of our privacy policy. Your continued visits to the ASSH website after changes are posted to this policy will signify your acceptance of those changes. 

**Contact information:**  
ASSH  
6300 North River Road, #600  
Rosemont, IL 60018  
Telephone: (847) 384-8300  
Fax : (847) 384-1435 

**Effective Date:** August 27, 2004
